Register of the Frederick L. Anderson papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Chronological File, 1942-1945
  - 1944
    - November 6 (Box-folder 35: 6)
    - November 7 (Box-folder 35: 7)
    - November 8 (Box-folder 36: 1)
    - November 9 (Box-folder 36: 2)
    - November 10 (Box-folder 36: 3)
    - November 11 (Box-folder 36: 4-5)
    - November 12 (Box-folder 36: 6)
    - November 13 (Box-folder 36: 7)
    - November 14 (Box-folder 36: 8)
    - November 15 (Box-folder 37: 1)
    - November 16 (Box-folder 37: 2)
    - November 17 (Box-folder 37: 3)
    - November 18 (Box-folder 37: 4)
    - November 19 (Box-folder 37: 5)
    - November 20 (Box-folder 37: 6)
    - November 21 (Box-folder 37: 7)
    - November 22 (Box-folder 37: 8)
    - November 23 (Box-folder 37: 9)
    - November 24 (Box-folder 37: 10)
    - November 25 (Box-folder 38: 1)
    - November 26 (Box-folder 38: 2)
    - November 27 (Box-folder 38: 3)
    - November 28 (Box-folder 38: 4)
    - November 29 (Box-folder 38: 5)
    - November 30 (Box-folder 38: 6)
    - December 1-2 (Box-folder 38: 7)
    - December 3 (Box-folder 38: 8)
    - December 4 (Box-folder 39: 1)
    - December 5 (Box-folder 39: 2)
    - December 6 (Box-folder 39: 3)
    - December 7 (Box-folder 39: 4)
    - December 8 (Box-folder 39: 5)
    - December 9 (Box-folder 39: 6)
    - December 10 (Box-folder 39: 7)
    - December 11 (Box-folder 39: 8)
    - December 12 (Box-folder 39: 9)
    - December 13 (Box-folder 39: 10)
    - December 14 (Box-folder 40: 1)
    - December 15 (Box-folder 40: 2)
    - December 16 (Box-folder 40: 3)
    - December 17 (Box-folder 40: 4)
    - December 18 (Box-folder 40: 5)
    - December 19 (Box-folder 40: 6)
    - December 20 (Box-folder 40: 7)
    - December 21 (Box-folder 40: 8)
    - December 22 (Box-folder 41: 1)
    - December 23 (Box-folder 41: 2)
    - December 24 (Box-folder 41: 3)
    - December 25 (Box-folder 41: 4)
    - December 26 (Box-folder 41: 5)
    - December 27 (Box-folder 41: 6)
    - December 28 (Box-folder 41: 7)
    - December 29 (Box-folder 41: 8)
    - December 30 (Box-folder 42: 1)
    - December 31 (Box-folder 42: 2)
  - 1945
    - January 1 (Box-folder 42: 3)
    - January 2 (Box-folder 42: 4)
    - January 3 (Box-folder 42: 5)
    - January 4 (Box-folder 42: 6)
    - January 5 (Box-folder 43: 1)
    - January 6 (Box-folder 43: 2)
    - January 7 (Box-folder 43: 3)
    - January 8 (Box-folder 43: 4)
    - January 9 (Box-folder 43: 5)
    - January 10 (Box-folder 43: 6)
    - January 11-12 (Box-folder 44: 1)
    - January 13 (Box-folder 44: 2)
    - January 14 (Box-folder 44: 3)
    - January 15 (Box-folder 44: 4)
    - January 16 (Box-folder 44: 5)
    - January 17 (Box-folder 44: 6)
    - January 18 (Box-folder 45: 1)
    - January 19 (Box-folder 45: 2)
    - January 20 (Box-folder 45: 3)
    - January 21 (Box-folder 45: 4)
    - January 22 (Box-folder 45: 5)
    - January 23 (Box-folder 45: 6)
    - January 24 (Box-folder 46: 1)
    - January 25 (Box-folder 46: 2)
    - January 26 (Box-folder 46: 3)
    - January 27 (Box-folder 46: 4)
    - January 28 (Box-folder 46: 5)
    - January 29 (Box-folder 46: 6)
    - January 30 (Box-folder 46: 7)
    - January 31 (Box-folder 47: 1-2)
    - February 1 (Box-folder 47: 3)
    - February 2 (Box-folder 47: 4)
    - February 3 (Box-folder 47: 5)
    - February 4 (Box-folder 47: 6)
    - February 5 (Box-folder 47: 7)
    - February 6 (Box-folder 48: 1)
    - February 7 (Box-folder 48: 2)
    - February 8 (Box-folder 48: 3)
    - February 9 (Box-folder 48: 4)
    - February 10 (Box-folder 48: 5)
    - February 11 (Box-folder 48: 6)
    - February 12 (Box-folder 48: 7)
    - February 13 (Box-folder 49: 1)
    - February 14 (Box-folder 49: 2)
    - February 15 (Box-folder 49: 3)
    - February 16 (Box-folder 49: 4)
    - February 17 (Box-folder 49: 5)
    - February 18 (Box-folder 49: 6)
    - February 19 (Box-folder 49: 7)
    - February 20 (Box-folder 50: 1)
    - February 21 (Box-folder 50: 2)
    - February 22 (Box-folder 50: 3)
    - February 23 (Box-folder 50: 4)
    - February 24 (Box-folder 50: 5)
    - February 25 (Box-folder 50: 6)
    - February 26 (Box-folder 51: 1)
    - February 27 (Box-folder 51: 2)
    - February 28 (Box-folder 51: 3)
    - March 1 (Box-folder 51: 4)
    - March 2 (Box-folder 51: 5)
    - March 3 (Box-folder 51: 6)
    - March 4 (Box-folder 52: 1)
    - March 5 (Box-folder 52: 2)
    - March 6 (Box-folder 52: 3)
    - March 7 (Box-folder 52: 4)
    - March 8 (Box-folder 52: 5)
    - March 9 (Box-folder 52: 6)
    - March 10 (Box-folder 53 :1)
    - March 11 (Box-folder 53: 2)
    - March 12 (Box-folder 53: 3)
    - March 13 (Box-folder 53: 4)
    - March 14 (Box-folder 53: 5)
    - March 15 (Box-folder 53: 6)
    - March 16 (Box-folder 54: 1)
    - March 17 (Box-folder 54: 2)
    - March 18 (Box-folder 54: 3)
    - March 19 (Box-folder 54: 4)
    - March 20 (Box-folder 54: 5)
    - March 21 (Box-folder 54: 6)
    - March 22 (Box-folder 54: 7)
    - March 23 (Box-folder 55: 1)
    - March 24 (Box-folder 55: 2)
    - March 25 (Box-folder 55: 3)
    - March 26 (Box-folder 55: 4)
    - March 27 (Box-folder 55: 5)
    - March 28 (Box-folder 55: 6)
    - March 29 (Box-folder 55: 7)
    - March 30 (Box-folder 56: 1)
    - March 31 (Box-folder 56: 2)
    - April 1 (Box-folder 56: 3)
    - April 2 (Box-folder 56: 4)
    - April 3 (Box-folder 56: 5)
    - April 4 (Box-folder 56: 6)
    - April 5 (Box-folder 57: 1)
    - April 6 (Box-folder 57: 2)
    - April 7 (Box-folder 57: 3)
    - April 8 (Box-folder 57: 4)
    - April 9 (Box-folder 57: 5)
    - April 10 (Box-folder 57: 6)
    - April 11 (Box-folder 58: 1)
    - April 12 (Box-folder 58: 2)
    - April 13 (Box-folder 58: 3)
    - April 14 (Box-folder 58: 4)
    - April 15 (Box-folder 58: 5)
    - April 16 (Box-folder 59: 1)
    - April 17 (Box-folder 59: 2)
    - April 18 (Box-folder 59: 3)
    - April 19 (Box-folder 59: 4)
    - April 20 (Box-folder 59: 5)
    - April 21 (Box-folder 59: 6)
    - April 22 (Box-folder 60: 1)
    - April 23 (Box-folder 60: 2)
    - April 24 (Box-folder 60: 3)
    - April 25 (Box-folder 60: 4)
    - April 26 (Box-folder 60: 5)
    - April 27 (Box-folder 60: 6)
    - April 28 (Box-folder 60: 7)
    - April 29 (Box-folder 60: 8)
    - April 30 (Box-folder 60: 9)
- Eighth Air Force, Headquarters File, 1942-1944
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, strategic studies, military orders, printed matter, clippings, and other materials, relating to the operations of the Eighth Air Force in Europe. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Commanders' meetings, 1943 April-October (Box-folder 61: 1)
  - Fighters-on-hand estimates as of the first of the month, 1942 November - 1944 January (Box-folder 61: 2)
  - Heavy bomber operational reporting, 1942-1944
    - Volume I (Box-folder 61: 3-4)
    - Volume II (Box-folder 61: 5-6)
  - Industrial Damage Report No. 50 (Mannheim, Cologne and Gennevilliers), 1942 May 18-31 (Box-folder 62: 1)
  - Intelligence Operations Summaries, 1944
    - June (Box-folder 62: 2)
    - September (Box-folder 62: 3)
  - Media and press releases, 1943 (Box-folder 62: 4)
  - Monthly Summary of Operations, 1944 December (Box-folder 62: 5)
    Includes a summarization of the year.
  - New bombing technique, 1943 December (Box-folder 62: 6)
  - Operation "Starkey,", 1943 August-September (Box-folder 62: 7)
  - Operational Planning Committee, Enemy Fighter Reaction Study, 1943 September (Box-folder 62: 8)
  - Organizational chart (Box-folder 62: 9)
  - Plan for Winter Operations, 1944 December - 1945 April (Box-folder 62: 10)
  - R.A.F. bomber offensive against Germany, 1943 (Box-folder 62: 11)
  - Report of Tactical Operation in Support of First and Ninth United States Armies, Eschweiler Area, 1944 November 16 (Box-folder 63: 1)
  - Service Command, Officers' Refresher Course, Lectures and Outlines, 1942 September-October (Box-folder 63: 2)
  - Third Bombardment Division, Station Management Control Manual, 1944 March (Box-folder 63: 3)
  - "To Stop the Flow of Submarines, Which Valves Would You Turn?,", 1943 (Box-folder 63: 4)
- Eighth Bomber Command, Headquarters File, 1942-1944
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, strategic studies, military orders, printed matter, clippings, and other materials, relating to the operations of the Eighth Bomber Command in Europe. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Bombardment Division Commanders meetings, 1943 July-December (Box-folder 64: 1)
  - Bomber Command Narrative of Operations
    - 1942 August - 1943 January (Box-folder 64: 2)
    - 1943
      - February-July (Box-folder 64: 3)
      - August-October (Box-folder 64: 4)
      - November-December (Box-folder 64: 5)
  - Bremen Attack, 1943 October 8 (Box-folder 64: 6)
  - Combat and Group Commanders meetings, minutes, 1943
    - June-July (Box-folder 64: 7)
    - July-October (Box-folder 64: 8)
    - October-December (Box-folder 64: 9)
  - First Bombardment Wing, reports of operations, 1943
    - March 18 (Box-folder 64: 10)
    - March 28 (Box-folder 64: 11)
  - German Air Force, status of, 1943 October (Box-folder 64: 12)
  - Group Commanders meetings, minutes, 1943 April-August (Box-folder 64: 13)
  - Intelligence analysis, operations, 1942 September - 1943 January (Box-folder 65: 1)
  - Media and press releases, 1943 (Box-folder 65: 2)
  - Memoranda to the United States, 1943 (Box-folder 65: 3)
  - Murphy, Charles, "Bombing,", 1943 September 14 (Box-folder 65: 4)
  - Names and numbers of aircraft (Box-folder 65: 5)
  - Operational Research Section
    - Analysis of Eighth Bomber Command Operations from the Point of View of Bombing Accuracy, January 1, 1943 - October 15, 1943 (Box-folder 65: 6)
    - Group bomb plots and summaries, 1943
      - May-June (Box-folder 65: 7)
      - July (Box-folder 65: 8)
      - August-September (Box-folder 65: 9)
    - Heavy bomber missions during May 1943 (Box-folder 66: 1)
  - Operations, 1943
    - October, general (Box-folder 66: 2)
    - October 20, No. 117 (Duren, Rhineland) (Box-folder 66: 3)
    - November 3, No. 119 (Wilhelmshaven) (Box-folder 66: 4)
    - November 5, No. 121 (Gelsenkirchen, Munster) (Box-folder 66: 5)
    - November 7, No. 124 (Duren) (Box-folder 66: 6)
    - November 11, No. 127 (Munster) (Box-folder 66: 7)
    - November 13, No. 130 (Bremen) (Box-folder 66: 8)
    - November 16, No. 131 (Knaben, Rjukan) (Box-folder 66: 9)
    - November 19, No. 134 (Western Germany) (Box-folder 66: 10)
    - December (Box-folder 66: 11)
  - Operations and missions, 1943
    - May-June (Box-folder 66: 12)
    - July-August (Box-folder 66: 13)
    - July-August (Box-folder 67: 1)
    - August (Box-folder 67: 2-4)
    - September (Box-folder 67: 5-8)
    - September (Box-folder 68: 1-2)
    - October (Box-folder 68: 3-5)
    - November (Box-folder 68: 6-8)
    - December (Box-folder 69: 1-4)
  - Organizational chart (Box-folder 69: 5)
  - Seating arrangements at formal functions, 1943 September-October (Box-folder 69: 6)
  - Squadron insignia (Box-folder 69: 7-8)
  - Station Administrative Manual, 1943 April (Box-folder 69: 9)
  - Tactical mission reports, 1943-1944
    - 1943
      - April 5 (Box-folder 69: 10)
      - April 16 (Box-folder 70: 1)
      - April 17 (Box-folder 70: 2)
      - May 13 (Box-folder 70: 3)
      - May 14
        - Antwerp Mission (Box-folder 70: 4)
        - Kiel Mission (Box-folder 70: 5)
        - Kiel, Vilsen, Antwerp, Courtrai (Box-folder 70: 6)
        - Velsen (Box-folder 70: 7)
      - May 15
        - Courtrai Mission (Box-folder 70: 8)
        - Heligoland, Emden (Box-folder 70: 9)
      - May 17
        - Bordeaux, Haarlem, Lorient (Box-folder 70: 10)
        - Bremen Mission (Box-folder 70: 11)
        - Emden Mission (Box-folder 70: 12)
      - May 19
        - Flensburg Mission (Box-folder 70: 13)
        - Wilhelmshaven, Cuxhaven (Box-folder 70: 14)
      - May 21: Emden, Wilhelmshaven (Box-folder 70: 15)
      - May 29
        - Rennes Mission (Box-folder 70: 16)
        - St. Nazaire, La Pallice, Rennes (Box-folder 70: 17)
      - June 11: Wilhelmshaven, Cuxhaven (Box-folder 70: 18)
      - June 13: Bremen, Kiel (Box-folder 71: 1)
      - June 22: Huls, Antwerp (Box-folder 71: 2)
      - June 23: Villacoublay, Le Mans (Box-folder 71: 3)
      - June 25: Hamburg, Bremen (Box-folder 71: 4)
      - June 26: Villacoublay, Le Mans (Box-folder 71: 5)
      - June 28: St. Nazaire, Beaumont (Box-folder 71: 6)
      - June 29: Villacoublay, Le Mans (Box-folder 71: 7)
      - July 4: Le Mans, Nantes, La Pallice (Box-folder 71: 8)
      - July 10: Villacoublay, Caen, Abbeyville, Poix, Le Bourget (Box-folder 71: 9)
      - July 14: Villacoublay, Amiens, Glisy, Le Bourget (Box-folder 71: 10)
      - July 17: Hanover, Hamburg, Amsterdam (Box-folder 72: 1)
      - July 24: Heroya, Bergen, Trondheim (Box-folder 72: 2)
      - July 25: Hamburg, Kiel, Warnemunde, Wustrow (Box-folder 72: 3)
      - July 26: Hanover, Hamburg, Amsterdam (Box-folder 72: 4)
      - July 28: Kassel, Oschersleben (Box-folder 72: 5)
      - July 29: Kiel, Flensburg, Warnemunde (Box-folder 72: 6)
      - July 30: Kassel, Hamm (Box-folder 72: 7)
      - August 12: Gelsenkirchen, Bochum, Bonn (Box-folder 72: 8)
      - August 15: Flushing, Poix, Amiens/Glisy, Merville-Lille, Vitry en Artois (Box-folder 72: 9)
      - August 16: Le Bourget, Poix, Abbeville (Box-folder 72: 10)
      - August 17: Schweinfurt, Regensburg (Box-folder 72: 11)
      - August 19: Flushing, Gilze-Rijen (Box-folder 73: 1)
      - August 24: Villacoublay, Evreux, Conches, Bordeaux (Box-folder 73: 2)
      - August 27: Watten (Box-folder 73: 3)
      - August 31: Amiens/Glisy, Woensdrecht, Brussels (Box-folder 73: 4)
      - September 2: Conches, Lille, Vannes-Meulan, Woensdrecht (Box-folder 73: 5)
      - September 6: Stuttgart, Strasbourg (Box-folder 73: 6)
      - September 7: Brussels/Evere, Enemy Convoy off Dutch coast, Watten (Box-folder 73: 7)
      - September 8 - October 9: Night operations (Box-folder 73: 8)
      - September 9: Lille, Vitry-en-Artois, St. Omer, Abbeville, Paris, Beaumont-sur-Oise, Beauvais/Tille (Box-folder 73: 9)
      - September 15: Romilly-sur-Seine, Chartres, Chateau-Dun, Paris (Box-folder 73: 10)
      - September 16: Nantes, Cognac, La Pallice, La Rochelle (Box-folder 74: 1)
      - September 23: Nantes, Vannes/Meucon, Kerlin/Bastard (Box-folder 74: 2)
      - September 26: Rheims airdrome (Box-folder 74: 3)
      - September 27: Emden, Aurich, Esens (Box-folder 74: 4)
      - October 2: Emden (Box-folder 74: 5)
      - October 4: Frankfurt, Wiesbaden, Saarlautern, St. Dizier, Sarrequemines, Saarbrucken (Box-folder 74: 6)
      - October 8: Bremen, Vegesack (Box-folder 74: 7)
      - October 9: Anklam, Gdynia, Danzig, Marienburg (Box-folder 74: 8)
      - October 10: Munster, Coesfield, Enschede, Diversion (Box-folder 75: 1)
      - October 14: Schweinfurt, Diversion (Box-folder 75: 2)
      - October 20: Duren, Diversion (Box-folder 75: 3)
      - November 3: Wilhelmshaven (Box-folder 75: 4)
      - November 5: Gelsenkirchen, Munster (Box-folder 75: 5)
      - November 7: Duren, Wesel (Box-folder 75: 6)
      - November 11: Munster (Box-folder 75: 7)
      - November 13: Bremen (Box-folder 75: 8)
      - November 18: Oslo (Box-folder 75: 9)
      - November 19: Gelsenkirchen (Box-folder 75: 10)
      - November 26: Bremen (Box-folder 76: 1)
      - November 29: Bremen (Box-folder 76: 2)
      - November 30: Solingen (Box-folder 76: 3)
      - December 1: Solingen (Box-folder 76: 4)
      - December 5: Paris, Cognac, Bordeaux (Box-folder 76: 5)
      - December 11: Emden (Box-folder 76: 6)
      - December 13: Bremen, Kiel, Hamburg (Box-folder 76: 7)
      - December 16: Bremen (Box-folder 76: 8-9)
      - December 22: Osnabruck, Munster (Box-folder 77: 1)
      - December 24: Crossbow, Noball (Box-folder 77: 2)
      - December 30: Ludwigshafen (Box-folder 77: 3)
      - December 31: Cognac, Paris, St. Jean d'Angeley, Landes de Bussac (Box-folder 77: 4)
    - 1944
      - January 4: Kiel, Munster (Box-folder 77: 5)
      - January 5: Bordeaux/Merignac, Elberfeld, Kiel, Tours (Box-folder 77: 6)
      - January 7: Ludwigshafen (Box-folder 77: 7)
  - Target: Germany - The Army Air Forces Official Story of the VIII Bomber Command's First Year Over Europe, 1943 (Box-folder 77: 8)
  - "You Can't Miss It,", undated (Box-folder 77: 9)
- U.S. Strategic Air Forces in Europe, Headquarters File, 1943-1945
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, strategic studies, military orders, printed matter, clippings, and other materials, issued by the Headquarters of the U.S. Stratetic Air Forces in Europe. Arranged alphabetically.
  - General
    - 1944 (Box-folder 78: 1-2)
    - 1944-1945 (Box-folder 78: 3-4)
    - 1945 February-May (Box-folder 78: 5)
  - AAF Training Film Project 1688, "Target for Today,", 1944 (Box-folder 78: 6)
  - Agenda for discussion with Air Marshal Portal at meeting scheduled for January 20, 1945 (Box-folder 78: 7)
  - Air Intelligence Summaries, 1945 January
    - No. 61 (Box-folder 78: 8)
    - No. 62 (Box-folder 78: 9)
  - Air Service Command, Special Summary for "Frantic" Project by Colonel John S. Griffith, 1944 May (Box-folder 78: 10)
  - Bombing targets in Germany, Austria, Poland, Czechoslovakia and Hungary, 1943 (Box-folder 78: 11)
  - Centralization of control of the U.S. Army Air Forces operating in the war against Japan, 1944 November (Box-folder 78: 12)
  - Codes and communications (Box-folder 78: 13)
  - Combined bomber offensive survey, 1944 July-August (Box-folder 78: 14)
  - Combined Strategic Targets Committee, January 1945 (Box-folder 79: 1)
  - Command and control of the U.S.S.A.F. in Europe (Box-folder 79: 2)
  - Command directives, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 79: 3-5)
  - Correspondence, 1945
    - Baccash, Gabriel (Box-folder 79: 6)
    - Bagby, Sally (Box-folder 79: 7)
    - Bassett, H. H. (Box-folder 79: 8)
    - Beaverbrook, Lord (Box-folder 79: 9)
    - Bernhard, Prince (The Netherlands) (Box-folder 79: 10)
    - Blumenthal, Charles (Box-folder 79: 11)
    - Bonesteel, Robert W. (Box-folder 79: 12)
    - Bottomley, N. H. (Box-folder 79: 13)
    - Bouscat, R. (Box-folder 79: 14)
    - Bufton, Sydney O. (Box-folder 79: 15)
    - Cabell, C. P. (Box-folder 79: 16)
    - Corman, Margaret L. (Box-folder 79: 17)
    - Curtis, E. P. (Box-folder 79: 18)
    - Dixon, George P. (Box-folder 79: 19)
    - Doolittle, James H. (Box-folder 79: 20)
    - Douglas, Kingman (Box-folder 79: 21)
    - Forbes, Viscount (Box-folder 79: 22)
    - Fritzsche, Carl F. (Box-folder 79: 23)
    - George, H. L. (Box-folder 79: 24)
    - Gill, Mary E. (Box-folder 79: 25)
    - Graham, Paul (Box-folder 79: 26)
    - Harriman, Averell (Box-folder 79: 27)
    - Harris, Arthur T. (Box-folder 79: 28)
    - Harris, Barbara (Box-folder 79: 29)
    - Hill, Edmund W. (Box-folder 79: 30)
    - Hughes, Richard D. (Box-folder 79: 31)
    - Kay, Marguerite (Box-folder 79: 32)
    - Knerr, Hugh J. (Box-folder 79: 33)
    - Laffon, Marcel (Box-folder 79: 34)
    - Leslie (Box-folder 79: 35)
    - McDonald, George C. (Box-folder 79: 36)
    - Maxwell, Alfred R. (Box-folder 79: 37)
    - Meardian, F. W. (Box-folder 79: 38)
    - Murphy, Charles (Box-folder 79: 39)
    - Murphy, Robert D. (Box-folder 79: 40)
    - Odom, Thetus (Box-folder 79: 41)
    - Pizzuto, Joseph R. (Box-folder 79: 42)
    - Portal, F. A. (Box-folder 79: 43)
    - Robb, J. M. (Box-folder 79: 44)
    - Robinson, J. R. (Box-folder 79: 45)
    - Sager, Captain (Box-folder 79: 46)
    - Scherer, Harris F. (Box-folder 79: 47)
    - Schlatter, David M. (Box-folder 79: 48)
    - Smith, Donald B. (Box-folder 79: 49)
    - Snider, Robert L. (Box-folder 79: 50)
    - Stockholm, Sweden, contacts (Box-folder 79: 51)
    - Stovall, W. H. (Box-folder 79: 52)
    - Tangye, Nigel (Box-folder 79: 53)
    - Vandenberg, Hoytt S. (Box-folder 79: 54)
    - Von Arbin, Captain and Mrs. (Box-folder 79: 55)
    - Webster, Robert (Box-folder 79: 56)
    - Weicker, Lowell P. (Box-folder 79: 57)
    - Westbrook, Wilfred (Box-folder 79: 58)
    - Whitney, John H. (Box-folder 79: 59)
    - Winant, John (Box-folder 79: 60)
    - Wood, Jack W. (Box-folder 79: 61)
  - Directorate of Operations, index of briefs for General Arnold (Box-folder 79: 62)
  - Directorate of Operations, index of briefs for General Arnold (Box-folder 80: 1)
  - Duties and Responsibilities of the Ninth Air Force and First Tactical Air Force (Prov) With Respect to Disarmament of the German Air Force, 1945 January (Box-folder 80: 2)
  - Eighth Air Force, Operations, 1945 April 1-13 (Box-folder 80: 3-4)
  - Eighth and Fifteenth Air Forces, heavy bomber fighters, effective sorties and tonnage on targets, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 80: 5)
  - Evaluation of the Effects of the Bomber Offensive on Operations "Overlord" and "Dragon" (Box-folder 80: 6)
  - Evaluation of German Capabilities, 1945 (Box-folder 80: 7)
  - Events during April 1-12, 1945 (Box-folder 80: 8)
  - Fifteenth Air Force
    - Heavy bomber operational reporting, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 80: 9)
    - Heavy bomber operational reporting, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 81: 1)
    - Movement to the U.K. and clearance from Russians to occupy bases in the Budapest area, 1945 January (Box-folder 81: 2)
    - Plan for Winter Operations, 1944 October 9 (Box-folder 81: 3)
  - Fighters, daily statistics, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 81: 4)
  - Flak Conference, 1945 March 15-16 (Box-folder 81: 5)
  - "Frantic" Project, 1944
    - February-May (Box-folder 81: 6-7)
    - April-May (Box-folder 81: 8)
    - Incoming messages, April-July (Box-folder 81: 9)
  - French Air Force Rearmament Plan, 1944 March-December (Box-folder 82: 1)
  - Guide to Intelligence Requirements in the War Against Japan, 1944 December 31 (Box-folder 82: 2)
  - Handbook on Air Disarmament Within the British Zone of Occupied Germany, 1945 April (Box-folder 82: 3)
  - "Jeeping the Targets in the Country That Was,", 1945 April (Box-folder 82: 4)
  - Joint Intelligence Sub-Committee, "Likely Conditions in the Areas of Germany Overrun by the British and American Armies,", 1945 April 4 (Box-folder 82: 5)
  - Joint Oil Target Committee, Working Committee, Weekly Bulletin, 1944 July - 1945 April (Box-folder 82: 6-7)
  - Memoranda, 1944 January-July (Box-folder 82: 8)
  - Mission orders, 1944 December - 1944 January (Box-folder 82: 9)
  - Ninth Air Force, Headquarters
    - Director of Intelligence, Intelligence Summary No. 124 (enemy situation, etc.), 1945 March 19 (Box-folder 82: 10)
    - Invasion activities, 1944 April-June (Box-folder 82: 11)
    - Nineteenth Tactical Air Command, Tactical Air Operations in Europe, 1944 August - 1945 May (Box-folder 83: 1)
    - Outline Plan for Operation "Eclipse,", 1945 February (Box-folder 83: 2-3)
  - Office of the Director of Intelligence
    - Evaluation of German Capabilities, 1945 (Box-folder 83: 4-5)
    - French plans for air transport service between Paris and Calcutta, 1945 (Box-folder 83: 6)
    - "Impact of the American War Machine on the German War Machine,", 1945 January 31 (Box-folder 83: 7)
    - Intelligence services, 1944 November-December (Box-folder 83: 8)
    - Requirements for air bases, facilities and privileges for U.S. air forces in Europe during the occupation period, 1945 May 7 (Box-folder 83: 9)
    - Special Report on Jet Propelled and Rocket Propelled Aircraft, 1944 August 26 (Box-folder 83: 10)
  - Operation "Eclipse" (Supreme Headquarters, Allied Expeditionary Force), 1944 November-December (Box-folder 83: 11)
  - Operational directives, 1944 December - 1945 January (Box-folder 83: 12-13)
  - Organizational chart (Box-folder 83: 14)
  - "Overlord,", 1944 (Box-folder 84: 1-3)
  - Photo mapping of Europe, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 84: 4)
  - Plan for the Completion of the Combined Bomber Offensive, 1944 March 5 (Box-folder 84: 5)
  - Post-hostilities planning, 1944 August-September (Box-folder 84: 6)